https://subscriptions.summitpartners.com/privacy-policy

Website Privacy Policy
Last Updated October 2020
For all California residents, please refer to Summit Partners' California Consumer Privacy Act Privacy Notice, which may be found here.
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to Summit Partners, L.P. and our affiliates (together, ‘our’, ‘us’, ‘we’ or ‘company’). This Privacy Policy is intended to help you understand what information we collect, how we use or process the information we collect, how we seek to secure the information we collect, and how you can update, manage and delete your information.
We may process your personal data when you visit the websites owned and operated by Summit Partners, L.P. including, https://www.summitpartners.com, (the “Website”). We are committed to ensuring that we process your personal data in accordance with applicable data protection legislation and privacy and data security laws.
Your use of the Website means that you accept and understand this Privacy Policy.
Please do not use the Website or provide us with any personal data if you do not accept this Privacy Policy.
For the purposes of applicable EU laws, Summit Partners, LP. will be a data controller of any personal data collected by us. If you have any questions regarding our use of your personal data, or this Privacy Policy, please contact Erin H. White at ewhite@summitpartners.com.
We rely on various legal bases under applicable data protection legislation in order to process your personal information (e.g., name, title, address, email, marital status, date of birth, country of residence, IP address, financial data, username, password, etc.), including our legitimate interests, contractual necessity and as required by law. We use the personal information we collect to operate our business and provide you with the services and products we offer and perform essential business operations. We do not collect any special categories of personal information about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). Nor do we collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.
If we require your personal information due to a legal requirement or obligation or in order to perform a contract with you, we will make you aware of this at the time we collect your personal data, and the possible consequences of you failing to provide this personal data. Further information about the legal bases under which we process your personal information is included in the section headed “Why we use your personal information”.
You do not need to take any action as a result of this Privacy Policy, but you do have certain rights as described below in the section headed “Your rights”.
We may from time to time update this Privacy Policy by posting an updated version of the Privacy Policy to the Website.
The date on which the Privacy Policy was last updated is set forth above.
Your use of the Website after any updated version is posted means that you accept and understand such updated Privacy Policy.
How We Obtain Your Personal Information
Information you provide to us
We collect your personal information when you decide to interact with us and we only collect the information necessary to carry out our business for the purposes set out below. You can provide us with personal information via this Website, email, post and telephone. We also collect information about you through automated technology.
We may collect the following personal data:
Your full name and contact details (email address, phone number, postal address, country of residence, etc.) may be provided when you complete forms available on the Website or when you contact us via email or provide such information during a phone call or in person meeting;
Personal data you provide when you contact us via the contact information listed on our website;
Technical information related to how you used the Website, specifically, the browser, device, internet connection, IP address, time zone setting, operating system and platform, etc. via cookies employed on the Website;
Details of visits to the Website, including how users are directed to the Website, the volume of traffic received, logs and the resources that you have accessed and the devices you have used to access the Website and
Personal data relating to: (i) your application for employment at Summit Partners L.P., (iii) your attendance at a Summit event; and/or (iv) the Summit Partners Alumni Network.
We may also collect personal data from third parties such as a CV received from a recruiting firm, background check information received from a background check service provider, information we view on social media, or details obtained from publicly available lists of individuals subject to trade restrictions. The data we collect from third parties is often in aggregate form and not individually identifiable, though at times may include personal data
Why we use your personal information
To the extent that you provide us with any personal information, through or in connection with this Website (i.e., via telephone, email or post) or through the provision of services to you, we may use such information for the following purposes:
Purpose
Legal Basis
Investment Due Diligence: To conduct due diligence activities in connection with an actual or prospective corporate transaction or investment with respect to which we are party to.
Legitimate interest
Build Relationships with Entrepreneurs: If you are an entrepreneur, we may contact you to provide information about Summit’s financing capabilities or general information that we think you may be interested in.
Legitimate interest
Improving the Website: We use information you provide to better understand your needs and provide you with better service, for example, we may use your personal data to improve the layout of our website based on the click path you utilized to access certain information within the Website.
Legitimate interest and/or consent (where we collect information using analytical cookies, see further below under ‘Cookies’)
Marketing: To keep a record of your relationship with us or to make suggestions and recommendations to you about events, goods or services that may be of interest to you or to conduct surveys and further analyse market trends and interests.
Legitimate interest and consent
Job Applications: To evaluate and respond to your application for employment with Summit Partners, L.P.
Legitimate interest
In Compliance with Applicable Law or Regulation: To verify your identity, manage threatened or actual litigation matters, or conduct internal audits or reviews.
To comply with legal obligations
Improved Security: To detect security incidents and to protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity.
To comply with legal obligations
No automated decision-making, including profiling, is used when processing your personal information.
Marketing
We will send you direct marketing communications based on your consent to keep you informed of our products and services in which you might be interested, or based on our legitimate business interests to tell you about certain events or to share news we believe you will be interested in. You may opt-in to certain kinds of marketing, and all forms of marketing at any time, by emailing maketing@summitpartners.com or at any time choose not to receive our marketing communications by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link provided in all our marketing emails.
Disclosure and transfer of personal information
Unfortunately, the transmission of information and data via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of any information or data transmitted to or through the Website; any transmission of information or data by you to or through the Website is at your sole risk.
Your personal information will be shared with and processed by our affiliates and certain service providers as necessary to fulfil the purposes set out in this policy, including professional advisors, recruitment firms, consultants and data hosting providers. We make sure anyone who provides a service to, or for us, enters into an agreement with us and meets our standards for data security. To the extent your personal information is transferred to countries outside of the EEA, such transfers will only be made in accordance with applicable data privacy laws. For further information about the safeguards/derogations used, please contact Erin H. White at ewhite@summitpartners.com.
To the extent any personal information is transferred from Summit Partners, L.P. or an affiliate within the EEA to a Summit Partners, L.P. entity or an affiliate outside the EEA, this transfer is legitimised and your personal information is adequately protected under the terms of the EU controller-to-controller model contract clauses.
We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, or when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, request from a regulator, national security, for the purposes of public importance or any other legal or investigatory process involving us. Should we, or any of our affiliated entities, be the subject of a takeover, divestment or acquisition we may disclose your personal information to the new owner of the relevant business and their advisors on the basis of our legitimate interest.
Security and retention of personal information
We are committed to protecting the personal information you entrust to us. We endeavour to implement robust and appropriate technologies and policies, and seek to ensure the information we have about you is protected to the extent possible from unauthorized access and improper use. In addition, we limit access to your personal information to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions, and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.
We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal information breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.
We will keep your personal information only for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required by law. We will not keep more information than we need for those purposes. For further information about how long we will keep your personal information, please contact Erin H. White at ewhite@summitpartners.com.
Capacity
The Website is only intended for individuals who are at least 18 years of age. We do not knowingly encourage or solicit visitors to the Website who are under the age of 18 or knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18 without parental consent. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from an individual under the age of 18, we will delete that information.
Cookies
Information regarding how you access this Website and your hardware and software is automatically collected through the use of cookies or other technologies or tools.
A cookie is a small text file that certain websites save on your device when you visit those websites. Cookies automatically collect information regarding how you access the Website (e.g., browser type, access times, and Internet Protocol (IP) address). We use cookies to improve the Website performance and to remember you when you return to the Website. You can confirm your website cookie preference through the interface in the cookies banner provided on the homepage of the Website.
If you prefer not to receive cookies through the Website, you can also set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser when you visit the Website. If you turn off cookies (or refuse to accept a request to place a cookie), you may not have access to some features on the Website and some of our services.
You may wish to visit www.aboutcookies.org, which contains comprehensive information about types of cookies, how they are used, and how you manage your cookie preferences.
(1) Necessary cookies used by the Website
We use necessary cookies to provide users with the services available through the Website and to use some of their features. These necessary cookies are essential for using and navigating the Website. Without these cookies, basic functions of the Website would not work. Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the Website, users cannot refuse them without impacting how the Website functions. For example, when a visitor logs into a password-protected area of the Website, we use a cookie to confirm the login status of that visitor in order to display password-protected content.
(2) Statistic and Analytic Cookies used by the Website
Statistic and analytic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information both anonymously and at the individual level, if that individual has agreed to the use of cookies via the Website’s cookie notification banner. The Website utilizes third-party analytics services (such as those of Google Analytics or HubSpot) to collect and analyse how users use the Website. The information generated by the statistic and analytic cookies about your use of the Website (including your IP address, browser type, domain name, etc.) will be transmitted to and stored directly by these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Website, including by noting the third-party website from which you arrive, analysing usage trends, measuring performance, assisting with fraud protection and providing certain features or information to you.
Such third-party vendors may also transfer this information to other third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on such service provider’s behalf.
On the Website we use the cookies listed below:
Name
Type
Provider
Purpose
Duration
_cfduid
Neccesary
Cloudfare
Helps detect malicious visitors to our website and minimizes blocking legitimate users
30 days
_fine_summit_session
Neccesary
Fine Design
Enables website functionality and analytics tracking
Session
summit_portal_unlock
Neccesary
Jackrabbit Design
Preserves the login state of a user for password-protected sections of the Website
2 years
_ga
Static (anonymous)
Google Analytics
Used to distinguish users
2 years
_gat
Static (anonymous)
Google Analytics
Used by Google Analytics to throttle request rate
1 day
_gid
Static (anonymous)
Google Analytics
Used to distinguish users
1 day
vuid
Static (anonymous)
Vimeo
Used by Vimeo to collect analytics tracking information.
2 years
wordpress_logged_in
Neccesary
Wordpress
Indicates and identifies when a Website administrator is logged into the Website.
Session
wordpress_sec
Neccesary
Wordpress
Store authentication details, limited to the administrator console area.
Session
wordpress_test_cookie
Neccesary
Wordpress
Checks if cookies are enabled on the browser to provide appropriate user experience to administrators
Session
wpe-auth
Neccesary
Wordpress
Used as part of the Wordpress Engine to authenticate administrator logins
Session
wp-settings
Neccesary
Wordpress
Customizes the view of the admin interface and the front-end of the website.
Session
wp-settings-time
Neccesary
Wordpress
Customizes the view of the admin interface and the front-end of the website.
Session
__hs_opt_out
Neccesary
HubSpot
This cookie is used by the opt-in privacy policy to remember not to ask the visitor to accept cookies again.
13 months
__hs_do_not_track
Neccesary
HubSpot
This cookie can be set to prevent the tracking code from sending any information to HubSpot.
13 months
__hs_initial_opt_in
Neccesary
HubSpot
This cookie is used to prevent the banner from always displaying when visitors are browsing in strict mode.
7 days
__hstc
Static (opt-in)
HubSpot
Visitor tracking. Contains the domain, utk, initial timestamp (first visit), last timestamp (last visit), current timestamp (this visit), and session number (increments for each subsequent session.
13 months
hubspotutk
Static (opt-in)
HubSpot
Keeps track of a visitor's identity. It is passed to HubSpot on form submission and used when deduplicating contacts.
13 months
__hssc
Static (opt-in)
HubSpot
Keeps track of sessions. Used to determine if HubSpot should increment the session number and timestamps in the __hstc cookie.
30 minutes
__hssrc
Static (opt-in)
HubSpot
Whenever HubSpot changes the session cookie, this cookie is also set to determine if the visitor has restarted their browser.
End of session
For more information about how Google Analytics data on our site, please visit https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites.
For more information about HubSpot’s cookie and privacy policy, please visit https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy.
Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. The Website does not currently recognize or respond to browser initiated DNT signals.
Should this change in the future, we will inform users through an updated version of this Privacy Policy.
Your rights
You have the right to access the personal information we hold about you, and there are a number of ways you can control the way in which and what information we store and process about you. To exercise these rights and controls, please contact Erin H. White at ewhite@summitpartners.com.
Access: You have the right to ask for a copy of the personal information that we hold about you free of charge, however we may charge a ‘reasonable fee’, if we think that your request is excessive, to help us cover the costs of locating the information you have requested.
Correction: You may notify us of changes to your personal information if it is inaccurate or it needs to be updated.
Deletion: If you think that we shouldn’t be holding or processing your personal information any more, you may request that we delete it. Please note that this may not always be possible due to legal obligations.
Restrictions on use: You may request that we stop processing your personal information (other than storing it), if: (i) you contest the accuracy of it (until the accuracy is verified); (ii) you believe the processing is against the law; (iii) you believe that we no longer need your data for the purposes for which it was collected, but you still need your data to establish or defend a legal claim; or (iv) you object to the processing, and we are verifying whether our legitimate grounds to process your personal information, override your own rights.
Object: You have the right to object to processing, including: (i) for direct marketing; (ii) for research or statistical purposes; or (iii) where processing is based on legitimate interests.
Portability: If you wish to transfer your personal information to another organisation (and certain conditions are satisfied), you may ask us to do so, and we will send it directly if we have the technical means.
Withdrawal of consent: If you previously gave us your consent (by a clear affirmative action) to allow us to process your personal information for a particular purpose, but you no longer wish to consent to us doing so, you can contact us to let us know that you withdraw that consent.
We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal information (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.
Notification of changes
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to collect personal information or use any collected information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify applicable users. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.
Contact us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact Erin White at ewhite@summitpartners.com or +1 617 824 1000.
Complaints
Should you wish to lodge a complaint with regards to how your personal information has been processed by us, please contact your local supervisory authority. In the UK, this is the Information Commissioner’s Office – https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us.
